Romanskyy Andriy

Tallinn, Estonia +37258785853 andrey.romanskyy@icloud.com

PROFILE

Applying for Junior Python Developer.

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

Python, Django, MySQL, Git, Terminal - more than 500 hours self studying, without commercial experience.

ADDITIONAL INFO

Passionate about technology, learning.

Have the ability to work in a team, identify problems, create plans, schedules and implement ones.

Interested in programming with Python, analytics and data.

English, level B1. Native language in Russian.

Manager with 15 years experience.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

August 2019 - present

Self-education in Python, SQL with no commercial experience.

Winester OÜ. Tallinn, Estonia - September 2017 - present.

Project manager in the field of electricity and communications (ehitustööde juht).

Personnel management. Interaction and negotiation with the customer's representative, the customer.

LLC "Nikelectro". Nikolaev, Ukraine - 2016 - 2017.

Chief engineer.

Organisation of work, forward planning, reporting documentation, personnel management.

LLC "Lex-practice" Nikolaev, Ukraine - 2011 - 2015.

Director of a law firm.

Company resource management, business management. Enterprise development planning. Reporting documentation. Personnel Management.

LLC «Svetoluxe-Electromontage". Nikolaev, Ukraine - 2007 - 2011.

Electrical engineer.

Organisation, planning and execution of 0.4 kV electrical work (range of work from installing a socket to installing a substation).

EDUCATION

Udacity, USA, online training.

Programming for Data Science with Python, Nanodegree Program - 2020.

2002 - 2005 Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding, Ukraine, Nikolaev

Specialist Degree, electrician.

1993 -1997 Nikolaev college of transport infrastructure

Dnieper National University of Railway Transport named after Academician V. Lazaryan

Bachelor's Degree, junior electrician.

RECOMMENDATIONS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/romanskyy-a/

https://github.com/Romanskyy